Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Dairy Queen Blizzard flavors
but lower in calories and higher in
protein. This is the Reese's Caramel
Craze Blizzard. Let me show you how to
make it. Starting off with a classic
vanilla base just like Dairy Queen does.
Mine includes Fairlife milk, sweetener,
salt, chef gum, and a little vanilla
bean paste. You just need to blend that
all together. Throw it in the freezer
for at least 16 hours. Once it's
completely frozen, just take it out, run
it under hot water for 30 seconds to a
minute, and then throw it in your creamy
on the light ice cream setting. It'll
probably come out a little bit powdery
like mine did, so you can just scrape
down the sides with a butter knife. And
then, assuming it's close to being done,
like mine was, you can haul out a hole
in the center and add your mixins. We're
using some mini peanut butter cups, some
rolos, or any kind of chocolate covered
caramel, and then my worldrenowned
chocolate chip hack. So, all of those go
into that hole and then you can just run
it on the mixing setting and then you're
done. Which Dairy Queen Blizzard flavor
do you want me to recreate next?